export const defaultDecks = {
  'Days of the week(EN to PT)': {
    title: 'Days of the week(EN to PT)',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Monday',
        answer: 'Segunda-feira'
      },
      {
        question: 'Wednesday',
        answer: 'Quarta-feira'
      },
      {
        question: 'Saturday',
        answer: 'Sábado'
      },
      {
        question: 'Tuesday',
        answer: 'Terça-feira'
      },
      {
        question: 'Thursday',
        answer: 'Quinta-feira'
      },
      {
        question: 'Friday',
        answer: 'Sexta-feira'
      },
      {
        question: 'Sunday',
        answer: 'Domingo'
      }
    ]
  },
  'Prime Numbers (2-20)': {
    title: 'Prime Numbers (2-20)',
    questions: [
      { question: 'Number 5?', answer: 'Yes' },
      { question: 'Number 7?', answer: 'Yes' },
      { question: 'Number 14?', answer: 'No' },
      { question: 'Number 18?', answer: 'No' },
      { question: 'Number 9?', answer: 'No' },
      { question: 'Number 8?', answer: 'No' },
      { question: 'Number 10?', answer: 'No' },
      { question: 'Number 15?', answer: 'No' },
      { question: 'Number 6?', answer: 'No' },
      { question: 'Number 19?', answer: 'Yes' },
      { question: 'Number 16?', answer: 'No' },
      { question: 'Number 13?', answer: 'Yes' },
      { question: 'Number 2?', answer: 'Yes' },
      { question: 'Number 4?', answer: 'No' },
      { question: 'Number 11?', answer: 'Yes' },
      { question: 'Number 17?', answer: 'Yes' },
      { question: 'Number 12?', answer: 'No' },
      { question: 'Number 3?', answer: 'Yes' }
    ]
  }
}
